Archives Organization File Additional records 5956
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Box 15, Folder (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Item 2: American Labor Unioins: An Outline of Growth and Structure, Publication (Box 15, Folder 4)
    By Reed C. Richardson. ILR Bulletin 30. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Trade Union Structure and Government (Part 1), Publication (Box 15, Folder 4)
    By John Hughes. Research Papers 5. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Trade Union Structure and Government (Part 2), Publication (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Item 5: Paraprofessionals, Their Organization, ad the Unions, Publication (Box 15, Folder 4)
    By Alan Gartner; Frank Riessman. "Social Policy" No. 3. Item is in English.
- Box 15, Folder (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: The Vital Links of the AFL-CIO, Publication (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Item 2: Building a Union of Textile Workers, Publication (Box 15, Folder 5)
    By Soloman Bankin. Report of two years progress to the convention of the United Textile Workers of America. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Handbook on Central Labor Bodies: Functions and Activities, Publication (Box 15, Folder 5)
    By Joan G. Kilpatrick; Miles C. Stanley. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Managers and Shop Stewards, Publication (Box 15, Folder 5)
    By Arthur Marsh. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Structure of AFL Unions, Publication (Box 15, Folder 5)
    By David J. Saposs; Sol Davison. May 15, 1939; Research Memorandum No. 8. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: Industrial Unionism: The Vital Problem of Organized Labor, Publication (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Item 7: Planning Inside the Unions, Publication (Box 15, Folder 5)
    By Political and Economic Planning. Broadsheet No. 249; May 10, 1946. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: The Merger Story, Publication (Box 15, Folder 5)
    By International Chemical Workers Union. A special report to convention delegates. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: The New Beginning, Publication (Box 15, Folder 5)
    By Walter P. Reuther. Address. Item is in English.
  - Item 10: Proceedings of the Merger Convention, Publication (Box 15, Folder 5)
    By California Labor Council on Political Education. Item is in English.
  - Item 11: Agreement to Merge Constitution Convention Rules and Order of Business, Publication (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Item 12: The Future of Organized Labor, Publication (Box 15, Folder 5)
    By John L. Lewis. Item is in English.
  - Item 13: American Labor Unions: An Outline of Growth and Structure, Publication (Box 15, Folder 5)
    By Reed C. Richardson. Bulletin 30. Item is in English.
  - Item 14: Agreement to Merge Constitution Convention Rules and Order of Business, Publication (Box 15, Folder 5)
    By California Labor Federation. Item is in English.
  - Item 15: Efforts Toward Merger 1935-1955, Publication (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Item 16: President Green Sounds Warning Against Continued Existence of Committee for Industrial Organization, Publication (Box 15, Folder 5)
    By William Green. Address. Item is in English.
  - Item 17: Industiral Unions Mean Unity, Publication (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Item 18: Industrial Unionism in the American Labor Movement, Publication (Box 15, Folder 5)
    By Theresa Wolfson; Abraham Weiss. Item is in English.
- Box 15, Folder (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Impact of Longshore Strikes on the National Economy, Publication (Box 15, Folder 6)
    By US Department of Labor. Item is in English.
- Box 15, Folder (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Fact Sheet on Collective Bargaining in the Longshore Industry, Publication (Box 15, Folder 7)
    By Bureau of Labor Statisticss. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Collective Bargaining in the Longshore industry, Publication (Box 15, Folder 7)
    By Longshore Industry. Item is in English.
- Box 15, Folder (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Trade Unions in Libraries, Publication (Box 15, Folder 8)
    By Erik Spicer. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Labor's Right to Organize, Publication (Box 15, Folder 8)
    By William Leiserson. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: The Development of National Labor policy, Publication (Box 15, Folder 8)
    By Slichter Summer. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Analysis, Publication (Box 15, Folder 8)
    By Federal Labor Legislation. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: The Development of National Labor Policy, Publication (Box 15, Folder 8)
    By Sumner Slichter. An Address at Upenn. Item is in English.
- Box 15, Folder (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Legal Services and the Labor Movement, Publication (Box 15, Folder 9)
    By National Resource Center for Conumers of Legal Services. Item is in English.
- Box 15, Folder (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: Leaves of Absence for Union Officers, Publication (Box 15, Folder 10)
    By Mildred Galloway. Item is in English.
- Box 15, Folder (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: A Survey of the Pockebook Industry in the United States, Publication (Box 15, Folder 11)
    By Isabel Taylor. Item is in English.
- Box 15, Folder (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: White-Collar Redundancy, Publication (Box 15, Folder 12)
    By Dorothy Wedderburn. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Redundancy, Publication (Box 15, Folder 12)
    By The Action Society Trust. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Layoff Policies and Practices, Publication (Box 15, Folder 12)
    By Robert Aronson. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Redundancy, Publication (Box 15, Folder 12)
    By The Acton Society Trust. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Job Dislocation Among Older Workers, Publication (Box 15, Folder 12)
    By Louis Ferman, Seymour Faber. Item is in English.
- Box 15, Folder (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: An Analysis of Quit and Layoff Rates in US Manufacturing Industries, Publication (Box 15, Folder 13)
    By Farrell Bloch. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Layoffs RIFS and EEO, Publication (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Item 3: Layoffs RIFS and EEO, Publication (Box 15, Folder 13)
    By The Bureau of National Affairs. Fair employment practice manual. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Alternatives to Layoffs, Publication (Box 15, Folder 13)
    By Edith Lynton. Item is in English.
- Box 15, Folder (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: Consider the Laundry Workers, Publication (Box 15, Folder 14)
    By Jane Filley and Therese Mitchell. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Report to the Industrial Commissioner, NY, Publication (Box 15, Folder 14)
    By Laundry Minimum Wage Board. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Survey of the Laundry Industry, Publication (Box 15, Folder 14)
    By Isabel Taylor, Maxwell Hurwitz, Saul Held. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Analysis of Physical Demands and Working Conditions present in Laundry Industry Jobs, Publication (Box 15, Folder 14)
    By Michigan State Employment Service. Item is in English.
- Box 15, Folder (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - Item 1: Triple Victory Program, Publication (Box 15, Folder 15)
    By R J Thomas, GEO Addes. Item is in English.
- Box 15, Folder (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - Item 1: Labor's Concern, Publication (Box 15, Folder 16)
    By The Commonwealth of Massachusetts. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Report of Survey of the Union Health Center and Hospital Benefit Program, Publication (Box 15, Folder 16)
    By Bureau of Public health Economics. Item is in English.
- Box 16, Folder (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: The Trade Union Movement in th European Community, Publication (Box 16, Folder 1)
- Box 16, Folder (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Union Growth in Canada, 1921 - 1967, Publication (Box 16, Folder 2)
    By Economics and Research Branch. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Bulletin of the John R Commons Labor Reference Center, Publication (Box 16, Folder 2)
    By Esther Thelen. Item is in English.
- Box 16, Folder (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: The Foreman, Publication (Box 16, Folder 3)
    By United State Training Service. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Human Understanding in Industry, Publication (Box 16, Folder 3)
    By William Vermilye. Item is in English.
- Box 16, Folder (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: What the Bussinessman Should Know About the Taft-Hartley Act, Publication (Box 16, Folder 4)
    By Thomas McDermott. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Worse Than Taft-Hartley, Publication (Box 16, Folder 4)
    By Walter Reuther, Arthur Goldberg. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: New Labor Relations Policies and Remedies Suggested by Different Industrial Settings, Publication (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Item 4: Employee Relations Bulletin, Publication (Box 16, Folder 4)
    By L. R. Boulware. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: How the NLRB Repealed Taft-Hartley, Publication (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Item 6: A Taft-Hartley Case Study, Publication (Box 16, Folder 4)
    By Industrial Union Department, AFL - CIO. What has happened to the American federation of Hosiery workers. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: Taft-Harley Act in Action, Publication (Box 16, Folder 4)
    By Jack Barbash. Item is in English.
- Box 16, Folder (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: What Should be the New Labor Legislation?, Publication (Box 16, Folder 5)
    By RoundTable. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: has Taft-Hartley Act Served Public Interest?, Publication (Box 16, Folder 5)
    By The Commonwealth Club of carlifonia. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Revision of the Taft-Hartley Act, Publication (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Item 4: The New congress and the Taft-Hartley Law, Publication (Box 16, Folder 5)
    By RoundTable. AN NBC Radio discussion. Item is in English.
- Box 16, Folder (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Digest of Special Panel Session, Publication (Box 16, Folder 6)
    By Congress of American industry. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Effect of the Taft-hartley Law on the Workers in Specific Southern Textile Mills, Publication (Box 16, Folder 6)
    By Jacobs and Jacobs. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: The Effect of the Taft-Hartley Law on Workers in textile Mills, Publication (Box 16, Folder 6)
    By jacobs and jacobs. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Selected Papers Presented before the Labor-management Round Table, Publication (Box 16, Folder 6)
    By Graduate school of Business, Columbia University in the City of New York. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Changes to make in Taft-Hartley, Publication (Box 16, Folder 6)
    By Theodore Iserman. Item is in English.
- Box 16, Folder (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: why the Trade Union Have been Be-organized, Publication (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Item 2: Old Before its Time: Collective bargaining at 28, Publication (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Item 3: Labor and the American Way, Publication (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Item 4: Facts About SIF, Publication (Box 16, Folder 7)
    By Svenska Industritjanstemannaforbundet. Swedish Union of Clerical and Technical Employees in Industry. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Trade Unions and the Individual in English Law, Publication (Box 16, Folder 7)
    By Cyril Grunfield. A study of recent developments. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: Topical Problems of The International Trade movement, Publication (Box 16, Folder 7)
    By Vukmanovic Tempo. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: The Status of Trade Unions in Pakistan, Publication (Box 16, Folder 7)
    By Sidney Sufrin, Syed Sarwar. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: Fact Sheet, Publication (Box 16, Folder 7)
    By Miners International Federation. Item is in English.
- Box 16, Folder (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Music in industry, Publication (Box 16, Folder 8)
    By R. L. Cardinell. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Music in Industry, Publication (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Item 3: American Society of Composers, Author and Publishers, Publication (Box 16, Folder 8)
    By R. L Cardinell. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Music in Relation to Employee Attitude, Piece-Work Productio, and Industry Accidents, Publication (Box 16, Folder 8)
    By Henry Clay smith. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Music in War Plants, Publication (Box 16, Folder 8)
    By Wheeler Beckett. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: Boosting worker Efficiency: A Sound Approach, Publication (Box 16, Folder 8)
    By Joseph Roberts. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: A Research Study of its Effectiveness and Acceptance, Publication (Box 16, Folder 8)
    By Ernest Werner. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: Let Them Have Music, Publication (Box 16, Folder 8)
    By Don samson. reprinted from Forbes. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: Music in Industry, Publication (Box 16, Folder 8)
    By Policyholders Service Bureau - Group Insurance Division - Metropolitan Life Insurance Company. Item is in English.
  - Item 10: Music and the Factory Worker, Publication (Box 16, Folder 8)
    By Forrest Kirkpatrick. Item is in English.
  - Item 11: The Application of Music in Industry and its Effect Upon the Morale and Efficiency of the Worker, Publication (Box 16, Folder 8)
    By J. H Scott Jr and S. Libbey. Item is in English.
- Box 16, Folder (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: A Study of Western Electric's Performance, Publication (Box 16, Folder 9)
    By McKinsey & Company. Item is in English.
- Box 16, Folder (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: The Story of Management, Publication (Box 16, Folder 10)
    By Du Pont Research Division. Item is in English.
- Box 16, Folder (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: A Bibliography, Publication (Box 16, Folder 11)
    By L. Urwick. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: The Corporation and the Republic, Publication (Box 16, Folder 11)
    By Scott Bughanan. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: The Expert and the Administrator, Publication (Box 16, Folder 11)
    By Jaleel Ahmad. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Ratios of Staff to Line personnel, Publication (Box 16, Folder 11)
    By Bruce Erwin DeSpelder. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Ratios of Staff to Line Employees and Stages of Diffrentiation of Staff Functions, Publication (Box 16, Folder 11)
    By Alton Baker; Ralph C. Davis. Item is in English.
- Box 16, Folder (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: The Law and Harry Bridges, Publication (Box 16, Folder 12)
    By Bridges-Robertson-Schmidt Defense Committee. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: The South Western Social Science Quaterly, Publication (Box 16, Folder 12)
    By The South western Social Science. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Safety and Health in Dock Work, Publication (Box 16, Folder 12)
    By Internaional Labor Force Geneva. Item is in English.
- Box 16, Folder (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: maintenance of Union Membership, Publication (Box 16, Folder 13)
    By Bryce Stewart; Walter Couper. Item is in English.
- Box 16, Folder (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: The Second John Storey memorial Lecture, Publication (Box 16, Folder 14)
    By Sir john Crowford. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Do you Still have the Right to Run your Plant?, Publication (Box 16, Folder 14)
    By National Association of Manufacturers. A Self-audit of Management Rights. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: An Employer's Rights in a National Labor Relations Board Relations Board Representation Electon, Publication (Box 16, Folder 14)
    By Charles G Bakaly; Alfred Phillips. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: The Nature of the Work of the Chief Executive, Publication (Box 16, Folder 14)
    By Ralph Cordiner. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Adventure in Thought and Action, Publication (Box 16, Folder 14)
    By Massachusetts Institute of Technology. The fifth anniverary of the school of industrial management. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: The Law of esponsible Authority, Publication (Box 16, Folder 14)
    By Fred Clark; Richard Stanton Rimanoczy. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: The Henry Laurence Grantt Memorial Gold Medal, Publication (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - Item 8: Contracting-out, Publication (Box 16, Folder 14)
    By Margaret Chandler; Leonard Sayles. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: Employers' Rights and Obligaions, Publication (Box 16, Folder 14)
- Box 16, Folder (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - Item 1: The Public be Served, Publication (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - Item 2: Basic Principles Newsletter, Publication (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - Item 3: Industry's Platform for 1938, Publication (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - Item 4: NAM and the Colleges, Publication (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - Item 5: Testimony Regarding Revision of LMRA before the Senate Labor and Public Welfare Committee and before the House Committee on Education, Publication (Box 16, Folder 15)
    By Ira Mosher. Given on Feb 18 & 25 1949 and March 15, 1949. Item is in English.
- Box 16, Folder (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - Item 1: Principles of Plant Protection, Publication (Box 16, Folder 16)
    By Industrial Security Division Office of Manpower Munitions Board. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Individual Freedom and the Common Defense, Publication (Box 16, Folder 16)
    By The Fund for the Republic. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: What is Labor Doing in th War?, Publication (Box 16, Folder 16)
    By War Production Board. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: To Parents in Wartime, Publication (Box 16, Folder 16)
    By Children's Bureau, United States Department of Labor. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Impact of the Military Program Upon Labor Market, Personnel Administration and Union Management Relations, Publication (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - Item 6: Impact of the Military Program Upon Labor Market, Personnel Administration and Union Management Relations, Publication (Box 16, Folder 16)
    By M. E Fields. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: Impact of the Military Program upon Labor Market, Personnel Administration and Union Management Relations, Publication (Box 16, Folder 16)
    By M.E. Fields. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: Teamwork for Victory, Publication (Box 16, Folder 16)
    By Automotive Council for War Production. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: Weapons That Win, Publication (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - Item 10: War Production Drive, Publication (Box 16, Folder 16)
- Box 16, Folder (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - Item 1: Men Jobs and Defense, Publication (Box 16, Folder 17)
    By US Social Security Board, Federal Security Agency. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Labor and the National Defense, Publication (Box 16, Folder 17)
    Eleventh Annual Institute of Labor. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Labor, Defense and Democracy, Publication (Box 16, Folder 17)
    By Robert La Follettee; Elinore Herrick; James Carey; Marx Lewis; Walter White. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Labor Leaders Discuss Natonal Defense in CBS Forum Broadcast, Publication (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - Item 5: The Problems and Organization of farming Out, Publication (Box 16, Folder 17)
    By Sidney Hillman. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: America Faces the Future, Publication (Box 16, Folder 17)
    By John Krout. A series of papers presented at the semi-annual meeting of the academy of political science April 16, 1941. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: Manning Industry for Defense, Publication (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - Item 8: The Negro and Defense, Publication (Box 16, Folder 17)
    By Council for Democracy, New York. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: National defense and America's Future, Publication (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - Item 10: Farming out Methods, Publication (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - Item 11: Defense and the Salaried Employee, Publication (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - Item 12: Labor in the Defense Crisis, Publication (Box 16, Folder 17)
    By T. R. carskadon. Item is in English.
- Box 16, Folder (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - Item 1: Manning the Arsenal for Democracy, Publication (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - Item 2: Effects of the Defense Program on Proces, Wages, and Profits, Publication (Box 16, Folder 18)
    By Meyer Jacobstein; Harold Moulton. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Suggested Emergency Fir Rent Legislation, Publication (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - Item 4: Extent of Week-end Shut-Downs in Selected Defense Industries, Publication (Box 16, Folder 18)
    By Frances Perkins Secretary; Isador Lubin. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Labor and National Defense, Publication (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - Item 6: Curtailment of Non-Defense Expenditures, Publication (Box 16, Folder 18)
    By Henry Seidemann. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: Priorities and Defense, Publication (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - Item 8: Labor in Wartime, Publication (Box 16, Folder 18)
    By Charles Noyes. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: Defense - One Year, Publication (Box 16, Folder 18)
    By Office of Emergency Management. Item is in English.
  - Item 10: Special Bulletins no. 1, 2 and 3, Publication (Box 16, Folder 18)
    By US National Defense Commission. Item is in English.
  - Item 11: Discussion over the Columbia Network, Publication (Box 16, Folder 18)
    By Columbia Broadcasting System. Discussion on January 26th, 1941. Item is in English.
  - Item 12: Economic Problems Generated by the Defense Program, Publication (Box 16, Folder 18)
    By Sumner Slichter. Item is in English.
  - Item 13: Labor Policy and national Defnse, Publication (Box 16, Folder 18)
    By Clark Dickinson. Item is in English.
  - Item 14: Protection of Industrial Plants and Public Buildings, Publication (Box 16, Folder 18)
    By United States Office of Civilian Defense. Item is in English.
  - Item 15: Protection of Industrial plants and Public Buildings, Publication (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - Item 16: Labor Policy and National Defense, Publication (Box 16, Folder 18)
    By The Ninth Fortune Round Table. Suppliment to Fortune, July 1941. Item is in English.
  - Item 17: Address before the National Society of Mechanical Engineers, Publication (Box 16, Folder 18)
    By henry Baker Jr. Item is in English.
  - Item 18: Economic Problems Generated by the Defense Program, Publication (Box 16, Folder 18)
- Box 16, Folder (Box 16, Folder 19)
  - Item 1: Workers and national Defense, Publication (Box 16, Folder 19)
    By United States Department of Labor. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Defense Planning - A nation in Need, Publication (Box 16, Folder 19)
    By Willard Arant. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Defense Planning and Labor Policy, Publication (Box 16, Folder 19)
  - Item 4: Wha Strikes Defense Industries?, Publication (Box 16, Folder 19)
    By Eleanor Troy; Jo Paqin. Bulletin of America's Town Meeting. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: facts About Labor and national Defense, Publication (Box 16, Folder 19)
  - Item 6: making America Strong, Publication (Box 16, Folder 19)
  - Item 7: labor relations and National Defense, Publication (Box 16, Folder 19)
  - Item 8: The Manpower and Mr. Hillman, Publication (Box 16, Folder 19)
    Reprinted from Fortune, November 1940. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: Functions and Activities, Publication (Box 16, Folder 19)
  - Item 10: American National Defense, Publication (Box 16, Folder 19)
    By Anne Baden. Item is in English.
  - Item 11: Labor Against War, Publication (Box 16, Folder 19)
  - Item 12: Expansion of the United States Navy, Publication (Box 16, Folder 19)
    By Grace Fuller; Florence Hellman. 1933-1939. Item is in English.
  - Item 13: Western Hemisphere Defense, Publication (Box 16, Folder 19)
    By Helen Conover. A Brief List of References. Item is in English.
  - Item 14: Selected Occupations Which have Significance in the National Defense Program, Publication (Box 16, Folder 19)
    By US Bureau of Labor Statistics. Item is in English.
  - Item 15: Consumers' Guide, Publication (Box 16, Folder 19)
    By National Defense Advisory Commission. Item is in English.
  - Item 16: Machine Tools, Publication (Box 16, Folder 19)
    By National Machine Tool Builders Association. Item is in English.
  - Item 17: Labor and the War, Publication (Box 16, Folder 19)
  - Item 18: Outline of Industrial Relations Policis in Defense Industries, Publication (Box 16, Folder 19)
    By Industrial Relation Section, Dept of Economics and Social Institutions. Item is in English.
  - Item 19: Industrial mobilization Plan Revision of 1939, Publication (Box 16, Folder 19)
    By Louis Johnson; Charles Edison. Item is in English.